{
    "id": "9ab9dd865eb849749cc099d01734c2c3",
    "title": "All And Whole",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "We canâ€™t spend ................................... time arguing.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "whole",
                "the whole",
                "whole the"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "28be535288b9476fba870657f963ecec"
        },
        {
            "question": "Why do you argue .......................... time?",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "all",
                "whole",
                "all the"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "e8c17823a44243c280f4a5e916391c09"
        },
        {
            "question": "........................................ thieves have been caught.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "The whole",
                "Whole",
                "All the"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "cd37a0948ce7466ca0243839c2debc22"
        },
        {
            "question": "............................. family attended the function.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "All",
                "All the",
                "Whole",
                "The whole"
            ],
            "correct": 3,
            "id": "e8e76aa88ca34c1eae57854b06d7c7da"
        },
        {
            "question": "You are ................................. responsible for this.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "whole",
                "wholly",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "fabdfde6fe074bcabf955ca61576397c"
        },
        {
            "question": "You have eaten ........................... loaf.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "whole",
                "a whole",
                "all a"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "48667e009d5542ea84008f0e58c3355e"
        },
        {
            "question": "......................... London was talking about her affairs.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "All",
                "All the",
                "The whole"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "d4f2cf4697344cfb9bd3af38928854bd"
        },
        {
            "question": "That is ............................. point.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "all",
                "whole",
                "the whole"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "8de32d8ed710417d98b3c263e70a00ec"
        },
        {
            "question": "It is ....................... in the mind.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "all",
                "whole",
                "the whole"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "f985fdd696a149689a762a75313065ec"
        },
        {
            "question": "If I were a millionaire, I would travel ..................... world.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "all",
                "whole",
                "the whole"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "0644922d2b054541985abeffb9e88789"
        }
    ]
}